A Guide to the Thomas H. Hunter Collection 1934-1995
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1970-1978, 17 TLS/TL (P) (Box-folder 48-4)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTES N.D., 3 AN (Box-folder 48-5)
- MEMOS SENT TO AND BY THOMAS H. HUNTER 1977-1980, 2 TM, AM, 3 TM (P) (Box-folder 48-6)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS, PAMPHLETS, AND CARDS 1969-1979, 6 Reprints/Pamphlets/Cards (Box-folder 48-7)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1968-1977, 11 TMs (P) (Box-folder 48-8)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1973, 7 TL (CC) (Box-folder 48-9)
  Nairobi
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1973, 2 TLS (Box-folder 48-10)
- NAIROBI PRESENTATION BY THOMAS H. HUNTER 1973/02, TMs (CC) (Box-folder 48-11)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTES IN THOMAS H. HUNTER'S HAND 1973/ca, 7 AN (Box-folder 48-12)
- [MGMWSHA WSH] TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1973/02/08, Mailgram (Box-folder 48-13)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1972-1973, 4 TLS (P) (Box-folder 48-14)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1971-1973, 16 TMs (P) (Box-folder 48-15)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1967, 2 TLS (Box-folder 48-16)
  National Academy of Sciences
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTES N.D., 2 AN (Box-folder 48-17)
- MEETING AGENDAS 1967, TMs (P) (Box-folder 48-18)
- MISCELLANEOUS PAMPHLETS AND ANNOUNCEMENTS 1972-1973, 2 Pamphlets, 2 Printed Cards (Box-folder 48-19)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1979, 2 TL (CC) (Box-folder 48-20)
  National Endowment for the Humanities
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1979-1980, 4 TLS (Box-folder 48-21)
- MEMOS AND CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1972-1975, 6 TLS/TL/TM (P) (Box-folder 48-22)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1973-1975, 7 TMs (P) (Box-folder 48-23)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS 1973-1975, 3 Reprints (Box-folder 48-24)
- MISCELLANEOUS PAMPHLETS 1977-1980, 11 Pamphlets (Box-folder 48-25)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1974-1976, 6 TL (CC) (Box-folder 48-26)
  National Foundation for Infectious Diseases
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1974-1976, 11 TLS (Box-folder 48-27)
- MISCELLANEOUS PAMPHLETS AND NEWSLETTERS 1975-1977/ca, 12 Pamphlets/Newsletters (Box-folder 48-29)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1974-1976, 19 TMs (P) (Box-folder 48-30)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 974-1976, 9 TLS (P) (Box-folder 48- 281)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1963, 4 TL (CC) (Box-folder 49-1)
  National Institutes of Health
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1962-1963, 6 TLS (Box-folder 49-2)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1962, 5 TMs (P) (Box-folder 49-5)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS 1958-1969, 4 Reprints (Box-folder 49-6)
- MEMO SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1962/06/21, TM (P) (Box-folder 49-7)
- EDWARD P. OFFUTT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1962/11/21, TLS (Box-folder 49-8)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS 1962, 2 Reprints (Box-folder 49-9)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1962, 3 TMs (P) (Box-folder 49-10)
- NATIONAL INSTITUTES OF HEALTH TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1962/11/24, Envelope (Box-folder 49-11)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1962-1965, 12 TL (CC) (Box-folder 49-12)
  National Institutes of Health NATIONAL INSTITUTE OF ARTHRITIS AND METABOLIC DISEASES 1962-1966
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1962-1966, 22 TLS (Box-folder 49-13)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTES 1964/ca, 3 AN (Box-folder 49-14)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTE AND RECEIPTS 1963, AN, 3 Printed Forms (Box-folder 49-15)
- MISCELLANEOUS INVOICES 1962-1964, 4 Printed Forms (Box-folder 49-16)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS AND CERTIFICATE 1963-1966, 3 Reprints, Certificate (Box-folder 49-17)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1963, 2 TLS (P) (Box-folder 49-18)
- MEMOS SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1964-1965, 2 TM (P) (Box-folder 49-19)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1963-1966, 24 TMs (P) (Box-folder 49-20)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1968, TL (CC), TM (CC) (Box-folder 49-21)
  National Institutes of Health SITE VISIT UNIVERSITY OF MINNESOTA DEPARTMENT OF PHYSIOLOGY SEPTEMBER 16-17, 1968
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968, 2 TLS (Box-folder 49-22)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTE AND ENVELOPE 1968/ca, AN, Envelope (Box-folder 49-23)
- STATEMENT OF TRAVEL AND EXPENSES 1968/09/18, Printed Form (Box-folder 49-24)
- VISIT SCHEDULES 1968, 3 TMs (P) (Box-folder 49-25)
- NATIONAL INSTITUTES OF HEALTH GRANT PROPOSAL 1968, TMs (P) (Box-folder 49-26)
- TRAVEL DOCUMENTS AND ENVELOPES 963, 2 Envelopes, 2 Printed Forms (Box-folder 49-31)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPY SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 962/07/06, TLS (P) (Box-folder 49-41)
- W. D. WHITEHEAD TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1967/04/21, TLS (Box-folder 50-1)
  National Science Foundation
- MEMOS AND CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968, 3 TLS/TM (P) (Box-folder 50-2)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1968-1972, 4 TMs (P) (Box-folder 50-4)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1978-1980, 6 TL (CC) (Box-folder 50-5)
  NEIDER, CHARLES
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1978-1980, 6 TLS (Box-folder 50-6)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS 1980/ca, 2 Reprints (Box-folder 50-7)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTE 1978/11/14, AN (Box-folder 50-8)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1981, 3 TMs (P) (Box-folder 50-10)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO THOMAS W. MOU 1971-1972, 2 TL (CC) (Box-folder 50-11)
  State University of New York Task Force 1971-1972
- THOMAS W. MOU TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1971-1972, 4 TLS (Box-folder 50-12)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1971/09/15, TMs (Box-folder 50-13)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1971, 7 TLS/TL (P) (Box-folder 50-14)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS AND PAMPHLETS 1971/ca, 2 Reprints/ Pamphlets (Box-folder 50-15)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1966-1976, 15 TL (CC) (Box-folder 50-16)
  O File
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1966-1979, 9 TLS (Box-folder 50-17)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1970-1976, 2 ALS (Box-folder 50-18)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPY SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1969, TLS (P), AN (Box-folder 50-19)
- MISCELLANEOUS NEWSCLIPPINGS AND NEWSLETTERS 1965-1968, 5 Newsclippings/Newsletters (Box-folder 50-20)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1967-1969, 8 TLS (P) (Box-folder 50-21)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1973-1974, 4 TL (CC) (Box-folder 50-22)
  Overseas Medical Fund
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1974-1977, 6 TLS (Box-folder 50-23)
- DICK BROWN TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1973/01/21, ALS (Box-folder 50-24)
- MISCELLANEOUS PAMPHLETS AND NEWSLETTERS 1974-1976/ca, 7 Pamphlets/Newsletters (Box-folder 50-25)
- MEMOS SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1981, 2 TM (Box-folder 50-26)
- MEMOS AND CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1972-1976, 6 TLS/TM (P) (Box-folder 50-27)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1972-1980, 14 TMs (P) (Box-folder 50-28)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1958-1977, 59 TL (CC) (Box-folder 50-29)
  P File
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1962-1981, 47 TLS (Box-folder 50-30)
- MISCELLANEOUS PAMPHLETS AND NEWSLETTERS 1975/ca, 3 Pamphlets/Newsletters (Box-folder 50-31)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1966-1974, 16 ALS (Box-folder 50-31)
- MEMOS AND CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1966-1973, 9 TLS/TM (P) (Box-folder 50-32)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS AND NEWSLETTERS 1969-1978, 6 Reprints/Newsletters (Box-folder 50-33)
- MEMOS AND CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1966-1976, 4 TLS/TM (P) (Box-folder 50-34)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1966-1975, 10 TMs (P) (Box-folder 50-35)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTES AND ANNOUNCEMENT N.D., 2 AN, Printed Card (Box-folder 50-36)
- CHARLES NEIDER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 980/11/07, ALS (Box-folder 50-91)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968, 2 TLS (Box-folder 51-1)
  Pan American Conference on the Teaching of Democracy
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968, 2 TL (P) (Box-folder 51-2)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTES N.D., AN, AN (P) (Box-folder 51-3)
- MISCELLANEOUS NEWSLETTER 1968, Newsletter (Box-folder 51-4)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1968, 4 TMs (P) (Box-folder 51-5)
- OSCAR GOMEZ-POVINA TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1976/07/09, TLS (Box-folder 51-6)
  Pan American Federation of Associations of Medical Schools, (PAFAMS)
- ANNUAL REPORT TO THE KELLOGG FOUNDATION 1976, TMs (P) (Box-folder 51-7)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1979, TMs (P) (Box-folder 51-8)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO JESUS GUZMAN 1969/07/03, TL (CC) (Box-folder 51-9)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 196601969, 9 TLS (Box-folder 51-10)
- GOLDSTUECKER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968/11/13, Telegram (Box-folder 51-11)
- HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968/ca, ANS (Box-folder 51-12)
- NOTIFICATION OF PERSONNEL ACTION 1971, Printed Form (Box-folder 51-13)
- MEMOS AND CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1966-1968, 3 TL/TM (P) (Box-folder 51-14)
- MEMOS SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1967-1969, 4 TM (P) (Box-folder 51-15)
- MISCELLANEOUS NEWSLETTERS 1965-1966, 9 Newsletters (Box-folder 51-16)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1966-1969, 19 TMs (P) (Box-folder 51-17)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1973-1977, 2 TLS (Box-folder 51-18)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1977, 2 TLS (P) (Box-folder 51-19)
- MISCELLANEOUS PAMPHLETS AND NEWSLETTERS 1970-1976, 3 Pamphlets/Newsletters (Box-folder 51-20)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1967-1976, 8 TMs (P) (Box-folder 51-21)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1977, 6 TL (CC) (Box-folder 52-1)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1976-1977, 11 TLS (Box-folder 52-2)
- FRANCISCO TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1977/03/22, ALS (Box-folder 52-3)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTES IN THOMAS H. HUNTER'S HAND 1977/ca, 2 AN, ANS (Box-folder 52-4)
- MEMOS AND CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1977, 9 TLS/TM (P) (Box-folder 52-5)
- MEMOS AND CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1976-1977, 4 TLS/TM (P) (Box-folder 52-6)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1975-1977, 14 TMs (P) (Box-folder 52-7)
- LUIS MANUEL MANZANILLA TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1977/08/19, Telegram (Box-folder 52-8)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1977-1978, 2 TL (CC) (Box-folder 52-9)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1977-1978, 2t TLS (Box-folder 52-10)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1977-1978, 35 TLS (P) (Box-folder 52-11)
- MEMOS SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1978, 4 TM (P) (Box-folder 52-12)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTES, CHECK, RECEIPT 1977, 4 AN, Check, Printed Form (Box-folder 52-13)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1976-1978, 11 TMs (P) (Box-folder 52-14)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1976-1977, 5 TL (CC) (Box-folder 52-15)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1976-1978, 15 TLS (Box-folder 52-16)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTES 1977, AN, TN (Box-folder 52-17)
- GONZALEZ/AUVERT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1977/04/02, Telex (Box-folder 52-18)
- MEMOS AND CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1976-1977, 26 TLS/TM (P) (Box-folder 52-19)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1976-1977, 4 TMs (P) (Box-folder 52-20)
- MEETING AGENDA 1976, 2 Pamphlets (Box-folder 52-21)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1979, 7 TLS (Box-folder 53-1)
- MEMOS AND CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1979, 13 TLS/TM (P) (Box-folder 53-2)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS AND NEWSLETTERS 1978, 2 Reprints/Newsletters (Box-folder 53-3)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1979, 7 TMs (P) (Box-folder 53-4)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1977-1978, 9 TLS (Box-folder 53-5)
  Pan American Federation of Associations of Medical Schools, 1978 (PAFAMS)
- FRANK TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1978/03/03, ALS (Box-folder 53-6)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS 1977, 2 Reprints (Box-folder 53-7)
- PANAMERICAN FEDERATION OF ASSOCIATIONS OF MEDICAL SCHOOLS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., Envelope (Box-folder 53-8)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1978, 19 TLS (P) (Box-folder 53-9)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1976-1978, 4 TMs (P) (Box-folder 53-10)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1979-1980, 7 TL (CC) (Box-folder 53-11)
  Pan American Federation of Associations of Medical Schools, 1979 (PAFAMS)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1979-1980, 19 TLS (Box-folder 53-12)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1978-1979, 5 TMs (P) (Box-folder 53-13)
- MEMOS AND CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1978-1979, 37 TLS/TM (P) (Box-folder 53-14)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO ABRAHAM HORWITZ 1969-1970, 2 TL (CC) (Box-folder 54-1)
  Pan American Health
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1964-1970, TL (CC), 5 TLS (Box-folder 54-2)
- MEMOS AND CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1964-1966, 3 TLS/TM (P) (Box-folder 54-3)
- RAY ALLEN TO THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., ALS (Box-folder 54-4)
- NOTES IN THOMAS H. HUNTER'S HAND N.D., AMs (Box-folder 54-5)
- TEMPORARY ADVISOR FORMS 1970/09, 2 Printed Forms (Box-folder 54-6)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS, PAMPHLETS, POSTCARD 1960-1966, PC, 8 Pamphlets/Reprints (Box-folder 54-7)
- MISCELLANEOUS FORMS N.D., 2 Printed Forms (Box-folder 54-8)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1964-1966, 14 TMs (P) (Box-folder 54-9)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1969, 10 TMs (P) (Box-folder 54-10)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESP0NDENTS 1966-1967, 9 TL (CC) (Box-folder 54-11)
  Pan American Health 1966
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1966-1967, 6 TLS (Box-folder 54-12)
- MEMOS AND CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1966-1967, 6 TLS/TM (P) (Box-folder 54-13)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1966, 12 TMs (P) (Box-folder 54-14)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1966/01/03, TMs (P) (Box-folder 54-15)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS AND PAMPHLETS 1966, 4 Reprints/Pamphlets (Box-folder 54-16)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1966-1973, 6 TL (CC) (Box-folder 55-1)
  Pan American Health Organization
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1966-1973, 14 TLS (Box-folder 55-2)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINT N.D., Reprint (Box-folder 55-3)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTES IN THOMAS H. HUNTER'S HAND N.D., 4 AN (Box-folder 55-4)
- MEMOS AND CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1967-1968, 4 TLS/TM (P) (Box-folder 55-5)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1967, 8 TMs (P) (Box-folder 55-6)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1967, 9 TMs (P) (Box-folder 55-7)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO WILLIAM PARSON 1973-1980, 8 TL (CC) (Box-folder 55-8)
  PARSON, WILLIAM
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1973-1980, 5 TLS (Box-folder 55-9)
- WILLIAM PARSON TO THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., ALS (Box-folder 55-10)
- EDWARD W. HOOK TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1974-1975, 2 TLS (Box-folder 55-11)
  Partners of the Americas
- PARTNERS 1975/04, Newsletter (Box-folder 55-12)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1976-1977, 4 TL (CC) (Box-folder 55-13)
  Pennsylvania State University External Review Board Meeting 1977
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1976-1977, 4 TLS (Box-folder 55-14)
- MEMOS AND CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1976-1977, 4 TLS/TM (P) (Box-folder 55-15)
- NOTES IN THOMAS H. HUNTER'S HAND N.D., AMs (Box-folder 55-16)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS AND PAMPHLETS 1973-1977, 7 Reprints/Pamphlets (Box-folder 55-17)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1975-1977, 7 TMs (P), TMs (Box-folder 55-18)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1965-1981, 12 TL (CC) (Box-folder 55-19)
  The Peripatetic Club
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1965-1978, 10 TLS (Box-folder 55-20)
- PERIPATETIC CLUB MEETING PROGRAMS 1965-1980, 11 Pamphlets (Box-folder 55-21)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTES AND POSTCARDS 1968-1980, 2 AN, 4 PCS (Box-folder 55-22)
- MEMO AND CORRESPONDENCE COPY SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1976-1977, 2 TLS/TM (P) (Box-folder 55-23)
- PERIPATETIC CLUB MINUTES 1966-1981, 11 TMs (P) (Box-folder 55-24)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1972-1979, 42 TLS (Box-folder 56-1)
  The Pharos
- CHALMERS [GEMMILL] TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1972/03/24, ALS (Box-folder 56-2)
- BILL TO THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., ALS (Box-folder 56-3)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1971, 2 ALS (P) (Box-folder 56-4)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTES N.D., 6 AN (Box-folder 56-5)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO JEAN N.D., ALS (P) (Box-folder 56-6)
- ANNOUNCEMENT OF ADDRESS CHANGE 1980/07/28, PC (Box-folder 56-7)
- MEMOS AND CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1970-1977, 20 TLS/TM (P) (Box-folder 56-8)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1972-1981, 33 TL (CC) (Box-folder 56-9)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1971-1972, 8 TMs (P) (Box-folder 56-10)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPTS BY THOMAS H. HUNTER 1972/ca, 9 AMs/TMs, 9 TMs (P) (Box-folder 56-11)
- MISCELLANEOUS JOURNALS AND REPRINTS 1968-1969, 3 Journals, 2 Reprints (Box-folder 56-12)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1964-1966, 3 TLS (Box-folder 56-13)
  Population 1959-1966
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1965-1966, 4 TMs (P) (Box-folder 56-14)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS AND PAMPHLETS 1959-1967, 19 Reprints/Pamphlets (Box-folder 56-15)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1967-1970, 4 TLS (Box-folder 57-1)
  Population 1967-1970
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTES 1970, AN, AN (P) (Box-folder 57-2)
- HENRY VAN ZILE HYDE TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1970/02/26, ANS (Box-folder 57-3)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1967-1970, 3 TLS (P) (Box-folder 57-4)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1967-1970, 14 TMs (P) (Box-folder 57-5)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS, PAMPHLETS, NEWSLETTERS 1966-1970, 28 Reprints/Pamphlets/Newsletters (Box-folder 57-6)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1971, TL (CC), 2 TM (CC) (Box-folder 57-7)
  Population 1971-
- MIRIAM BIRDWHISTLE TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1971, TLS, TM (Box-folder 57-8)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO LAW STUDENTS 1971/03/16, TM (P) (Box-folder 57-9)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTES IN THOMAS H. HUNTER'S HAND N.D., 4 AN (Box-folder 57-10)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1971/ca, 3 TMs (P) (Box-folder 57-11)
- MEMOS SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1972, 3 TM (P) (Box-folder 57-12)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS, PAMPHLETS, NEWSLETTERS 1971-1972, 13 Reprints/Pamphlets/Newsletters (Box-folder 57-13)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1955-1959, 12 TL (CC) (Box-folder 57-14)
  Population Council
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1955-1959, 8 TLS (Box-folder 57-15)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1958-1959, 3 TL (CC) (Box-folder 57-16)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTE N.D., AN (Box-folder 57-17)
- MISCELLANEOUS PAMPHLETS 1964-1971, 3 Pamphlets (Box-folder 57-18)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1966-1969, 3 TL (CC) (Box-folder 57-19)
  Population Crisis Committee
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1966-1969, 4 TLS (Box-folder 57-20)
- MEMOS SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1967-1970, 7 TM (P) (Box-folder 57-21)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1966-1970, 5 TMs (P) (Box-folder 57-22)
- WILLIAM H. DRAPER JR. TO THOMAS H. HUNTER; MISCELLANEOUS NOTE 1968, AN, Telegram (Box-folder 57-23)
- MISCELLANEOUS PAMPHLETS AND NEWSLETTERS 1967-1972, 7 Pamphlets/Newsletters (Box-folder 57-24)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO RAMIRO DELGADO-GARCIA 1975/01/17, TL (CC) (Box-folder 58-1)
  PRIMOPS (Programa de Investigaciones en Modelos de Prestacion de Servicios de Salud)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1975, 2 TLS (Box-folder 58-2)
- CONTRACT EMPLOYEE BIOGRAPHICAL DATA SHEET 1975/01/17, 4 Printed Forms (Box-folder 58-3)
- GRANT PROPOSAL 1974/12, TMs (P) (Box-folder 58-4)
- PHILIP R. LEE TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1964/07/30, TLS (Box-folder 58-5)
  Professorship of Dermatology and Syphilology
- NEWS RELEASE 1964/07/27, TMs (P) (Box-folder 58-6)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS AND JOURNALS 1959/ca, 2 Reprints, 2 Journals (Box-folder 58-7)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS AND NEWSCLIPPINGS 1965/ca, 4 Reprints/Newsclippings (Box-folder 58-8)
  President's Committee on Heart Disease, Cancer and Stroke
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1964/ca, 3 TMs (P) (Box-folder 58-9)
- BILL TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1965/04/14, AN (Box-folder 58-10)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO ANTONIO QUIROZ 1973/01/15, TL (CC) (Box-folder 58-11)
  Q File
- CORRESPONDENCE COPY SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1969/05/15, TL (CC) (Box-folder 58-12)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1966-1979, 25 TL (CC) (Box-folder 58-13)
  R File
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1970-1980, 30 TLS (Box-folder 58-14)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1967-1977, 9 ALS (Box-folder 58-15)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTES 1970-1971/ca, 5 AN (Box-folder 58-16)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1970-1977, 8 TLS (P) (Box-folder 58-17)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1967-1977, 10 TMs (P) (Box-folder 58-18)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS 1975-1979, 16 Reprints (Box-folder 58-19)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1958-1966, 27 TL (CC) (Box-folder 58-20)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1960-1965, 31 TLS (Box-folder 58-21)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1965/ca, 2 ALS (Box-folder 58-22)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1960-1965, 8 TLS/TL (P) (Box-folder 58-23)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1963, 2 TMs (P) (Box-folder 58-24)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINT 1963/08, Reprint (Box-folder 58-25)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1964-1971, 27 TL (CC) (Box-folder 58-26)
  R File NUMBER TWO
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1964-1970, 37 TLS (Box-folder 58-27)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1970/ca, 2 ALS (Box-folder 58-28)
- CHANGE OF LOCATION ANNOUNCEMENT 1968/04/26, PC (Box-folder 58-29)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1966-1970, 9 TLS/TL (P) (Box-folder 58-30)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS 1967-1970, 2 Reprints (Box-folder 58-31)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1964/ca, 4 TMs (P) (Box-folder 58-32)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1974-1979, 52 TL (CC) (Box-folder 59-1)
  Recommendations
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1964-1975, 22 TLS (Box-folder 59-2)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1974, 2 ALS, APCS (Box-folder 59-3)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTES 1974/ca, TN, 5 AN (Box-folder 59-4)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINT 1973/03/03, Reprint (Box-folder 59-5)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO ALHASAN SISAWO CEESAY; CORRESPONDENCE COPY SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1973-1974, 2 TLS (P) (Box-folder 59-6)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1974-1975, 9 TMs (P) (Box-folder 59-7)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1968-1971, 4 TL (CC) (Box-folder 59-8)
  Regional Educational Laboratory for the Carolinas and Virginia
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968-1971, 6 TLS (Box-folder 59-9)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS 1967, 3 Reprints (Box-folder 59-10)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1968-1971, 3 TMs (P) (Box-folder 59-11)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1962-1963, 15 TL (CC) (Box-folder 59-12)
  RICHARDSON, FRED CORRESPONDENCE
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1962-1963, 5 TLS (Box-folder 59-13)
- GUS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1963/02/12, ALS (Box-folder 59-14)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1963, 3 TL (CC) (Box-folder 59-15)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL AND RECEIPTS 1962, 2 TMs (P), 2 Printed Forms (Box-folder 59-16)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINT 1962/05, Reprint (Box-folder 59-17)
- THE ELUSIVE NATURE OF COOPERATION AND LEADERSHIP BY F.L.W. RICHARDSON 1977/01, TMs (P) (Box-folder 59-18)
  RICHARDSON, FRED
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1972-1974, 4 TL (CC) (Box-folder 59-19)
  ROCKEFELLER, DAVID
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1972-1974, 6 TLS (Box-folder 59-20)
- MEMO SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1973/01/19, TM (P) (Box-folder 59-21)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1972/ca, TMs, TMs (P) (Box-folder 59-22)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO JANE ALLEN 1971/11/29, TL (CC) (Box-folder 59-23)
  Rockefeller Foundation
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1971-1979, 6 TLS (Box-folder 59-24)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTE N.D., AN (Box-folder 59-25)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1975, 5 TLS (P) (Box-folder 59-26)